Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - #19361. Promoting medical professionalism and ethics in Vietnam, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - UNSW Global Pty Limited - University of New South Wales, 2008-2010; University of New South Wales
      University of New South Wales
      - #16939. Preparing for the Rights to Human Health and Development Conference, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - #17563. Health development and human rights conference, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - UPLIFT International, 1999-2010
      UPLIFT International
      - #5185 (#99-366) Medical Needs. "Vietnam Disaster Relief", 1999-2000 (Box 235, Folder 21)
    - Victoria University of Wellington, 2002-2005
      Victoria University of Wellington
      - #11526. Vietnam information capacity, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - #11526. Capacity development and enrichment for Vietnamese information professionals, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - #11526. Capacity development and enrichment for Vietnamese information professionals, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam Ministry of Health, Administration of Preventive Medicine, 2005-2007; Vietnam. Bộ y tế. Cục y tế dự phòng và môi trường
      Vietnam. Bộ y tế. Cục y tế dự phòng và môi trường
      - #13930. Strengthen the coordinating capacity of the Vietnam Ministry of Health for injury prevention, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Viet Nam Ministry of Health, Committee on Smoking and Health, 2008-2009; Vietnam. Bộ y tế
      Vietnam. Bộ y tế
      - #15332 Best Practice in Implementing Smoke-free Policies in Viet Nam, 2008-2009 (Box 235, Folder 22)
    - Viet Nam Ministry of Health, Department of Planning and Finance, 2009-2010; Vietnam. Bộ y tế. Vụ kế hoạch-tài chính
      Vietnam. Bộ y tế. Vụ kế hoạch-tài chính
      - #17482 Development of the Joint Annual Health Review (2010-2012), 2009-2010 (Box 235, Folder 23)
    - Viet Nam National Institute of Ophthalmology, 2006-2007; Bệnh viện mắt trung ương (Vietnam)
      Bệnh viện mắt trung ương (Vietnam)
      - #15323 Develop the National Action Plan for Blindness Prevention and Eye Care Treatment in Viet Nam, 2006-2007 (Box 235, Folder 24)
    - Viet Nam Public Health Association, 2003-2006; Hội y té̂ công cộng Việt Nam
      - #12227. Infrastructure and capacity development grant, 2003-2006 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
      - #15337 Institutional Capacity Building for Viet Nam Public Health Association, 2008-2009 (Box 235, Folder 25)
    - Viet Nam Union of Friendship Organizations, 2003-2009; Liên hiệp các tỏ̂ chức hữu nghị Việt Nam
      Liên hiệp các tỏ̂ chức hữu nghị Việt Nam
      - #12226. Construction of a NGO development center, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - #12226 Construction of a NGO Development Center, 2003-2007 (Box 235, Folder 26)
      - #14154. Supplementary construction funding for the VUFO Information Resource Center, 2005-2009 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - International Center/Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation, 2005-2007; Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation
      Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation
      - #13926. Modelling community mental health and rehabilititation in Danang and Khanh Hoa provinces, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Viet Nam Women's Union, 2009; Hội liên hiệp phụ nữ Việt Nam
      Hội liên hiệp phụ nữ Việt Nam
      - #17701 Fulfilling the Rights of the Ageing Poor, 2009 (Box 235, Folder 27)
    - Vinh Long Provincial Health Department - So Y Te Vinh Long, 2008-2010; Vĩnh Long (Vietnam: Province). Sở Y Tế
      Vĩnh Long (Vietnam: Province). Sở Y Tế
      - #16661. Improve commune level facilities for primary health care in Vinh Long, 2008-2010 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Walter and Eliza Hall Institute of Medical Research, 2002-2004
      Walter and Eliza Hall Institute of Medical Research
      - #10535. Malaria control in Vietnam, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
        Malaria
      - #13259 Strengthening program and research capacity in parasitic disease surveillance and control in Viet Nam - Ph II, 2004-2008 (Box 235, Folder 28)
    - World Health Organization, 2007-2008
      World Health Organization
      - #15334 Improving pre-hospital trauma care services in Viet Nam, 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 29)
        First Aid Training